

PERSONAL DETAILS

- Name
 Alfonso Scornavacca
- Address
 Urquiza 1078
 Rosario, 2000
- **Phone number** +54 9 3467 41-9938
- **Email**alfondrums@gmail.com
- Date of birth
 15/07/1989
- Place of birthSan José de la Esquina
- **†∔ Gender** Male
- MationalityArgentino
- Marital status
 Unmarried
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/ir /alfonso-scornavacca/

LANGUAGES

ingles



ALFONSO SCORNAVACCA

I am a very sociable person, so I easily adapt to new work groups. I started as a web developer using JavaScript and its frameworks as my main language, but I also have experience in low-code tools such as Power Automate, Power App, and Sharepoint.

I also have experience in JavaScript, mainly with ReactJS and TypeScript



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Developer

Radium Rocket, Rosario

I completed a training course provided by Radium Rocket. It consists of learning how to use different technologies to create an API, both backend and frontend, working as a team using a GitHub repository. Among the technologies and languages used are HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, Express, ReactJS, GIT, GitHub, Trello, Scrum.

Feb 2022 - Present

Developer

Raona, Spain

Web development, use of various technologies such as .NET, Sharepoint Framework, Power Automate, Power Apps and others.



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Dec 2022 - Present **Programming Technician**

Teclab, Rosario

Technical career focused on structure and development of web and

desktop applications

Mar 2003 - Dec 2008 Estudios secundarios

E.E.T N° 476 Miguel Castellanos, San jose de la esquina

Secondary studies in the field of Communications, $\mbox{\sc Arts}$ and $\mbox{\sc Design}.$



SKILLS

PostgreSQL	****
HTML	****
CSS	****
Java Script	****
React JS	****
Express JS	****
Node JS	****
GIT	****
GitHub	****
Sharepoint	****

Power App

Power Automate

Azure

★★★★

★★★★



CERTIFICATES

Microsoft Intune

2021

React escuela DevRock

DevRock is a virtual school in which they offer several courses on web development, I currently took the HTML, CSS, JS and React Js courses

2021

Radium Rocket Full stack developer JS

Training provided by the company Radium Rocket that consists of learning how to use different technologies to create a web application, both backend and frontend, working in a group using a GitHub repository. Among the technologies and languages used are: HTML, CSS, JS, NodeJS, Express, ReactJS, GIT, GitHub, Trello, Scrum.

2023

MS-500 Security Administrator Associate

Deploy, manage, and monitor security and compliance solutions for Microsoft 365 and hybrid environments. The Microsoft 365 Security Administrator proactively protects identity and access, implements threat protection, manages information protection, and enforces compliance. The Microsoft 365 Security Administrator collaborates with the Microsoft 365 Enterprise Administrator, business stakeholders, and other workload administrators to plan and implement security strategies.

Functional experience with Microsoft 365 workloads and Microsoft Sign In

ID. Have implemented security for Microsoft 365 environments, including hybrid environments. Have a working knowledge of Windows clients, Windows servers, Active Directory, and PowerShell.

2022

AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals

This exam is a common starting point on a path to a career in Azure. You can describe the architectural components of Azure and Azure services, such as:

Compute

Networking

Storage

You can also describe the features and tools for securing, governing, and managing Azure.

You should have skills and experience working with an area of IT, such as: Infrastructure management

Database management Software development

2022

MTA- JavaScript

Microsoft Certification, basic knowledge in JavaScript

2023

SC-200 Security Operations Analyst Associate

Certification Details

As a Microsoft Security Operations Analyst, you reduce organizational risk by:

Rapidly remediating active attacks in the environment.

Advising on improvements to threat protection practices.

Referring organizational policy violations to appropriate stakeholders.

You perform:

Triage.

Incident response.

Vulnerability management.

Threat hunting.

Cyber threat intelligence analysis.

As a Microsoft Security Operations Analyst, you monitor, identify, investigate, and respond to threats in multicloud environments using:

Microsoft Sentinel

Microsoft Defender for the Cloud

Microsoft 365 Defender

Third-party security solutions

In this role, you collaborate with business stakeholders, architects, identity administrators, Azure administrators, and endpoint

administrators to protect the organization's IT systems.

Microsoft 365

Azure cloud services

Windows and Linux operating systems

As a candidate, you should be familiar with:



PUBLICATIONS

On my LinkedIn account I have all the verified links to see my certifications. You can also see some of my developments on my GitHub